Guide to the Gregory E. Montes urban history and travel collection, 1798-1960.
Montes, Gregory E. urban history and travel collection
- Series IV. Additional Items, Miscellaneous, Ephemera Posters, Artwork
  - Country / Region: Canada Canada 125 newspaper, volume 1, number 3, July 1992 (Box 20)
    Includes Canada 125 bumper sticker, a celebration of Canada's Birthday.
  - United Nations Commemorative Envelopes 1 (Box 24)
  - United Nations Commemorative Envelopes 2 (Box 24)
  - United Nations Commemorative Envelopes 3 (Box 20)
  - First Day of Issue Envelopes 1 (Box 24)
    71 envelopes primarily commemorating events from American history
  - First Day of Issue Envelopes 2 (Box 24)
    66 envelopes primarily commemorating events from American and World history
  - Ralph Dyer First Day of Issue Covers (Box 24)
    Hand-drawn drafts of First Day covers, often accompanied by feedback, some drafts marked as never used.
  - Miscellaneous photos (Box 20)
    Cuba, San Diego, Miscellaneous United States, set of photos by Dominic Caesar including negatives, photos of paintings "New York City Skyline" and "San Diego Skyline" by Sean Selfridge, "Yosemite" by June Rubin
  - Artist business cards (Box 20)
    Business cards produced by artists, either standard 3.5" X 2" or 6" X 4" (with photographs of artwork). Includes: Studio Maha, Bronle Crosby business cards with examples of photography/painting, Jeffery Rule, Inc. Landscape Architecture business card "Bristletone Pine" preview,
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego Newspaper clippings: Beach and Bay Press, San Diego CityBeat, San Diego Reader, The San Diego Union "Desperation in Hanoi's Acts" (Box 20)
  - The Coca-Cola Company International Headquarters (Box 18)
    Packet of 20 photos with captions.
  - Miscellaneous Brochures: Attractions (Box 25)
    Includes brochures from Boston, San Diego, Dido Cabaret (Champs-Élysées, Paris)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures: Travel Maps and Info (Box 25)
    Includes: maps of Boston; Rostock, Germany; Madrid, Spain; Dublin, Ireland; Oahu, Hawaii; Texas; Airline brochures for United Air Lines Jets, Lufthansa
  - Artwork (Box 25)
    Includes: Miscellaneous brochures and advertisements of artists mostly from the San Diego area, a Christmas card from an Anglophone in France, 1944, Enrico Natali, Dirk Tiede
  - Postcard Packs (Box 24)
    Includes: Pretoria, South Africa; Shanghai, China; Rio de Janeiro, Brazil; Bruxelles, Belgium; Metropolitan Areas of Boston, Bridgeport, New York, Philadelphia, Baltimore, Washington DC
  - Matchboxes (Box 24)
    12 matchboxes with advertisements on them
  - Color Transparencies, September 27, 1964 (Box 24)
    A box of 14 color transparencies, marked as "World's Fair"
  - Japex 79 (Box 24)
    Commemorative card written in Japanese.
  - Manor House Quarterly: "Space", Spring 2012 (Box 25)
    Periodical Literary Magazine